Guide to the Kathryn Hulme Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographs, 1873-1974; Series V; 4.75; (20 boxes)
  - PUBLICITY
    - The Nun's Story (film), 1958-59 (Box 52, Folder 726-35)
    - The Nun's Story (film), 1958-59 (Box 53, Folder 736-41)
- Gurdjieff, 1922-78; Series VI; 0.75; (2 boxes)
  Boxes 54 and 55 contain Series VI, Gurdjieff. The series consists of correspondence, lecture notes, papers, memorabilia, and photographs.
  - Correspondence, 1937-78 (Box 54, Folder 743-57)
  - Gurdjieff "lecture notes", 1922-39, n.d. (Box 54, Folder 758-61)
  - Gurdjieff "lecture notes", 1922-39, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 762-70)
  - Papers and memorabilia, 1949-70, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 771-77)
  - Photographs, n.d. (Box 55, Folder 778-79)